my wife had a kid we still have it we
have a kid and I'm supposed to be a dad
now
huh I know I don't know how good a movie
like I'm addicted to sugar that's my
thing no drugs no alcohol just sugar I
love sugar I'm trying to stop cuz trying
to be a good example but it ain't gonna
happen by two years ago I was in the
grocery store in the cereal aisle and
they had frosted flakes with lucky charm
marshmallows in it yeah I just started
shaking I'm just now getting my life
back together blew my mind this is my
first kid only kid I've never been
around kids I was our only child
not a big family so it's been a lot of
learning going on I get yelled at for
stuff all the time like stuff I don't
think I should be getting yelled at for
I don't think it makes sense when he was
seven months old I was on the couch
screening my bottle and my wife came
here she's like what are you doing what
are you doing keeping it alive
[Laughter]
and this is what she was mad about this
blue mama she says I don't want him to
have too many baby bottles as he has too
many Baby Bowser season like the baby
bottle more than he likes the real thing
and then I'm not gonna be able to latch
on to the real thing because he's gonna
want the plastic baby bottle like we
don't have anything to worry about cuz
no son of mine don't worry
no son of anybody it's not that's
new moms don't worry about that it's not
even close and if it was you wouldn't be
able to eat baby bottles on the shelf
[Music]
every lonely guy in America be swiping
up all the baby bottles terribly what's
a hungry kids running around
he's three and a half now and he's just
I don't like him I mean I love him to
death but I don't like him right now
we're doing the terrible twos and three
that's a real thing he's uh-oh hey were
trying to potty train him it's not going
well cuz when he poops he poops like
this
and he's been such a little prick lately
that I don't think we're gonna teach him
the right way to do it
like good luck making friends again the
girl from when you coop like a fountain
good luck teach you to embarrass me my
favorite target I never forget hey did
you know that Drybar comedy has its own
app download it right now and watch save
and share clips and watch my whole
special again and then after that